Guide to the Max Lerner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, Accession 1982-M-005
  - Writings, 1942-circa 1980; Series II
    Writings (3.75 linear ft.) are arranged in seven sections: articles and columns, book reviews, books, diaries, panels and symposia, research files, and television. Material is arranged alphabetically within each section. The series consists of notes, drafts, some manuscript copies, and typescripts of Max Lerner's published and unpublished writings, some transcripts of his participation in conferences and symposia, and his research files and working notes. There are also several diaries, including a "nine-month journal of adventures of ideas in Asia, the Middle East, and Europe;" diary entries on Lerner's trips to Rome and India; and diary descriptions of his dreams.
    - Articles and columns
      - "Alvin Johnson is 95" [notes, research material, printed copy], 1967-1969, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - "Beyond the Power Principle" [notes], [1959?] (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Book reviewing [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Cambridge 'Apostles' [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Daley and Meany [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - "Down with Aging" [typescript], 1975 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - "George McGovern" [typescript], 1972 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Germans [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - "How Save the Hostages?" [sic][draft], Undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - "Human Needs" [draft, clipping], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Israel - [page of typsecript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - "Journalism as History" [typescript and notes about Watergate], Undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
      - "Kissinger on the Couch" [typescript], 1975 March 5 (Box 2, Folder 51)
      - "The Lecturer" [draft, notes, clipping], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - "Life Style" [typescript, clipping], 1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Moon landing [notes and galley proofs], 1969 (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - "My Next Fifty Years" [notes], 1967 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - "A New Birth of Values" series [typescript], 1974 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - "The Not Impossible Sheet" [draft], Undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - "On Growing and Crowding" [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Partisan Review Symposium [typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
      - The Perils of Obedience [typescript and notes--published as "Conformity" in McCalls ], 1967 (Box 2, Folder 60)
      - "Presidential Profile" [draft], Undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
      - "The Roots of the Riots" [typescript], 1965 (Box 2, Folder 62)
      - "Suspense Masters" [notes, draft, printed copy], 1965 (Box 2, Folder 63)
      - Swope, Harold [draft and typescript], Undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
      - "A Talk with Michael Manley" [notes and draft], Undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
      - Taylor, Elizabeth [notes, drafts, and typescripts for article], 1974 (Box 2, Folder 66)
      - Territorial Imperative by Robert Ardrey [typescript and notes by Lerner for Book-of-the-Month-Club essay], Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - "Third-World Case History" [typescript], Undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - "Time of the Assassin" [draft], Undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - "Tocqueville and American Civilization"
        - Article drafts, Circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 70)
        - Notes and research materials, 1962-1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
        - Working notes, 1962-1964, undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
        - Southern Review [notes and typescript for article], Circa 1965 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - TV Guide [draft and typescript], Undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - "Watergate Punishment" [typescript], 1975 February 26 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - "A Woman Leader" [notes and typescript], Undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Book reviews
      - Carson, Gerald, The Polite Americans [typescript], 1966 March (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Dean, Herbert, The Political Ideas of Harold J. Laski [typescript], Circa 1955 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Gooch, G. P., English Democratic Ideas in the Seventeenth Century [typescript], 1957 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Hughes, H. Stuart, Consciousness and Society [notes and typescript], Circa 1958 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Laski, H. J., Communism [typescript], Undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Lubin and Everett, The British Coal Dilemna [typescript], Undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Tugwell, Rexford, A Chronicle of Jeopardy: 1945-1955 [typescript], 1956 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Books
      - America as a Civilization
        - Chapter typescript ["Generals Ride Again"], Circa 1965-1975 (Box 3, Folder 84)
        - Notes, Circa 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 85)
        - Notes for revision, Circa 1965-1975 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Borch, Herbert von
      See: Accession 1982-M-005, Series II. Writings, 1942-ca. 1980 Folder 88
      - Democratic Elite [notes], 1960-1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
      - Education [notes and research for a proposed book], 1961-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 88 - 91)
      - Education [notes and research for a proposed book], Circa 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 92 - 97)
      - Marriage [notes and typescript for book chapter; review of Germaine Greer's The Female Eunuch ], 1965-1975 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Melanson, Philip, Political Science and Political Knowledge [notes and typescript for foreword], Circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin D. [chapter draft], Undated (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - Ted and the Kennedy Legend, Circa 1980
        - Background material (Box 4, Folder 101)
        - First draft - complete manuscript (Box 4, Folder 102 - 103)
        - Third draft - complete manuscript (Box 5, Folder 104)
        - Final draft - complete manuscript (Box 5, Folder 105)
        - Chapter drafts (Box 5, Folder 106 - 109)
        - Chapter drafts (Box 6, Folder 110 - 113)
        - Notes and drafts (Box 6, Folder 114 - 119)
        - Notes and drafts (Box 7, Folder 120 - 125)
      - Von Borcht, Herbert [typescript and notes for preface to The Unfinished Society, English translation of Die Unfertige Gesselschaft ], Circa 1962 (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - A World Politics Reader [notes], Undated (Box 7, Folder 127)
      - Zilliacus, Konni [typescript for introduction to Mirror of the Past ], Circa 1946 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Diaries
      - ["Diary of East and West"], 1961 (Box 7, Folder 129)
      - 1961-1962, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 130)
      - 1965 March 24-25 (Box 7, Folder 131)
      - 1968 October 29 (Box 7, Folder 132)
      - 1969 July 4-5 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Panels and symposia
      - "Did Gulliver Ever Come Home?", 1969
        - Malle, Louis [transcript of conversation with] (Box 8, Folder 134 - 136)
        - Notes, proposals, outlines [written and typed] (Box 8, Folder 137)
      - "Does the Socialist State Tend to Destroy Individual Initiative?" [reprint of town meeting], 1949 (Box 8, Folder 138)
      - "How Can We Clean Up College Sports?" [reprint of town meeting], 1951 (Box 8, Folder 139)
      - Jewish Center Association [typescript], 1968 (Box 8, Folder 140)
      - Marxism [Talcott Parsons' response to Lerner], Undated (Box 8, Folder 141)
      - Oakland Panel on Education [typescript], Undated (Box 8, Folder 142)
      - Optimal Society International Symposium [typed transcripts], 1969 July (Box 8, Folder 143 - 148)
      - Optimal Society International Symposium [typed transcripts], 1969 July (Box 9, Folder 149 - 153)
      - University of Chicago, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 154)
    - Research files
      - American history [notes], 1964 (Box 9, Folder 155)
      - American women [notes], Undated (Box 9, Folder 156)
      - Autobiography [notes], 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 157)
      - Death [notes for a proposed series], Undated (Box 9, Folder 158)
      - Kissinger [notes], 1972, undated (Box 9, Folder 159)
      - Patterns of Sexual Behavior [reader's notes], Undated (Box 9, Folder 160)
      - Spain [notes], 1958 (Box 9, Folder 161)
      - Veblen, Thorstein [notes, research materials], Undated (Box 9, Folder 162)
      - Washington sex story [notes, typescript], Undated (Box 9, Folder 163)
      - Miscellaneous, Circa 1959-1970 (Box 9, Folder 164 - 167)
    - Television
      - Age of Overkill [notes, outlines, scripts], 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 168)
      - American Civilization [memo on television series], 1959 (Box 9, Folder 169)
      - "Invitation to World Politics" [typescript], Undated (Box 9, Folder 170)
  - Lectures and Speeches, 1963-1973, undated; Series III
    Lectures and speeches (1.0 linear feet) consist of Max Lerner's notes and drafts for speeches and talks, especially commencement addresses. They are arranged alphabetically within three sections: Institution/Organization, Location, and Subject. A fourth section, Other, is arranged alphabetically by type of material and contains programs and printed material from commencements, conferences, and lectures.
    - Institution/Organization
      - Air Force War College [notes], 1967 June (Box 10, Folder 171)
      - Albright College, Reading, Pennsylvania [notes], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 172)
      - AMA Annual Personnel Conference [typescript, program], 1968 February (Box 10, Folder 173)
      - Arkansas, University of [notes], 1967 October (Box 10, Folder 174)
      - Bellagra conference [notes], 1963 July 2 (Box 10, Folder 175)
      - Carlow College [notes for commencement address], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 176)
      - CBS [notes, agenda], 1970 (Box 10, Folder 177)
      - Cleveland Associated [?][notes], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 178)
      - Cleveland PTA [notes], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 179)
      - College counselors [notes for speech to counselors], 1968 (Box 10, Folder 180)
      - Columbia University School of Journalism [notes], Undated (Box 10, Folder 181)
      - Cornell University [notes], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 182)
      - Dana Hall, Wellesley, Massachusetts [notes], 1968 June (Box 10, Folder 183)
      - Florida State University [notes], 1965 (Box 10, Folder 184)
      - Ford Hall [notes], 1967, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 185 - 186)
      - Foreign Service [notes], 1967 (Box 10, Folder 187)
      - "Fulbrights," Washington, D.C. [notes], 1967 (Box 10, Folder 188)
      - Governor's Conference on Aging, New York City [reprint], 1966 May (Box 10, Folder 189)
      - Hofstra University [notes], Undated (Box 10, Folder 190)
      - Howard University [draft, typescript], 1967 February (Box 10, Folder 191)
      - Industrial College of the Armed Forces [reprint], 1964 December (Box 10, Folder 192)
      - Liggett School [notes, program], 1968 (Box 10, Folder 193)
      - Maryland, University of [notes], 1967 June (Box 10, Folder 194)
      - Medical students [notes for speech to], 1969 (Box 10, Folder 195)
      - Michigan State [notes, draft], 1973 February (Box 10, Folder 196)
      - Missouri at Kansas City, University of [notes, draft, program], 1972 February (Box 10, Folder 197)
      - National Jewish Welfare Board [notes, draft, clippings], 1968 June (Box 10, Folder 198)
      - New England Association [printed copy], 1971 (Box 10, Folder 199)
      - North Carolina at Greensboro, University of [draft], 1968 (Box 10, Folder 200)
      - Northeastern Professors of Psychiatry [notes, transcript], 1968 April (Box 10, Folder 201)
      - Pennsylvania, University of [notes, program], 1971 April (Box 10, Folder 202)
      - Raritan Valley Regional Chamber of Commerce [notes, program], 1971 March (Box 10, Folder 203)
      - Russell-Sage Education Panel [notes], 1971 April (Box 10, Folder 204)
      - School Administrators [notes, transcripts], Undated (Box 10, Folder 205)
      - School of International Politics [notes], Undated (Box 10, Folder 206)
      - Staff College of Armed Forces [notes], 1968 (Box 10, Folder 207)
      - Stephens College [notes, typescript], 1965 (Box 11, Folder 208)
      - Stockbridge [notes], 1967 July (Box 11, Folder 209)
      - United Jewish Appeal [notes], 1968 (Box 11, Folder 210)
      - Virginia Polytechnic Institute [notes], 1967 (Box 11, Folder 211)
      - Washington Graduate School Department of Agriculture [notes], 1965 April (Box 11, Folder 212)
      - West Liberty State [notes], 1968 February (Box 11, Folder 213)
    - Location
      - [Carrden?], New York [notes, drafts], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 214)
      - Dearborn, Michigan [notes], 1968 (Box 11, Folder 215)
      - Detroit, Michigan [notes], 1967 (Box 11, Folder 216)
      - Duchess [draft for commencement address], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 217)
      - Green Bay, Wisconsin [draft for commencement address], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 218)
      - Hawaii [notes], Undated (Box 11, Folder 219)
      - Iowa City, Iowa [notes], 1969 (Box 11, Folder 220)
      - Missoula, Montana [notes], 1969 (Box 11, Folder 221)
      - Orlando, Florida [notes], 1969 (Box 11, Folder 222)
      - Palm Springs, Florida [notes], Undated (Box 11, Folder 223)
      - Rochester, New York [notes], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 224)
      - San Jose, California [notes], 1967 October (Box 11, Folder 225)
    - Subject
      - Aging [notes], 1968 May (Box 11, Folder 226)
      - Ecology [notes], 1969 (Box 11, Folder 227)
      - "Elan, Elite, Ethos" [notes, drafts, typescript], Undated (Box 11, Folder 228)
      - "How Can We Be Free?" [notes], Undated (Box 11, Folder 229)
      - "How Do You Face Evil?" [draft], 1972 September (Box 11, Folder 230)
      - "The Inner and Outer World of the American Student" [typescript], 1967 January (Box 11, Folder 231)
      - Israel [notes], Undated (Box 11, Folder 232)
      - "The Jewish Presence in the Context of Social Change" [notes], 1970 (Box 11, Folder 233)
      - "Jews in the Modern World" [notes], Undated (Box 11, Folder 234)
      - Moratorium [notes], 1969 (Box 11, Folder 235)
      - "Realities of Power" [notes], 1968 (Box 11, Folder 236)
      - "Religion and Ideology" [typescript], Undated (Box 11, Folder 237)
      - Washington urban planning [notes], 1967 August (Box 11, Folder 238)
      - Year 2000 [notes], 1971 (Box 11, Folder 239)
    - Other
      - Commencement programs, Circa 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 240)
      - Conference material
        - Posters, 1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 241)
        - Programs, Circa 1963-1973 (Box 11, Folder 242)
      - Lecture material [untitled]
        - Drafts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 243)
        - Notes, 1969-1973, undated (Box 11, Folder 244 - 246)
        - Typescripts, Undated (Box 11, Folder 247 - 249)
  - Teaching Materials, 1941-1974, undated; Series IV
    Teaching materials (0.5 linear feet) are comprised of Lerner's outlines, lecture notes, and syllabi for courses taught at various institutions, particularly Brandeis University and the New School for Social Research. They are arranged alphabetically by name of institution. Within an institution, the files are arranged by course title or number.
    - Brandeis University
      - American Civilization 2 [syllabi, notes, outlines], 1952-1959, undated (Box 12, Folder 250 - 253)
      - American history [notes], 1964-1966, undated (Box 12, Folder 254 - 256)
      - American Intellectual History in the Twentieth Century — History/Politics 163br [syllabi, notes], 1965 (Box 12, Folder 257)
      - American Social Theory [notes], Undated (Box 12, Folder 258)
      - Modern Revolutionary Systems — Social Science 233 [syllabi], Undated (Box 12, Folder 259)
      - Patterns of American Civilization — American Civilization 80br [class notes], 1964 (Box 12, Folder 260)
      - Social Theory in America [syllabi, notes], Undated (Box 12, Folder 261)
      - Theories of American Civilization — Politics 172a [syllabi, notes], 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 262 - 264)
      - United States Since World War II — History 163br [syllabi], 1966 (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - University of Florida — Social Foundation of Education [syllabi, notes], 1974 (Box 12, Folder 266)
    - Harvard University — Harvard Government S7 [syllabus], 1941 (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Indian School of International Studies, New Delhi, India [notes], 1957 (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - New School for Social Research
      - New School #1 [notes]
        - 1965 (Box 12, Folder 269)
        - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 270)
      - New School #3 [notes]
        - 1968 (Box 12, Folder 271)
        - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 272)
      - New School #4 [notes], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 273)
      - New School #5 [notes]
        - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 274)
        - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 275)
        - 1972 (Box 12, Folder 276)
      - New School #6 [notes]
        - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 277)
        - 1970 (Box 12, Folder 278)
      - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 279)
    - Pomona College — Issues in American Politics [syllabi, notes], 1974 (Box 12, Folder 280)
    - Miscellaneous [notes, lectures, syllabi], 1941-1942, undated (Box 12, Folder 281)
- Additional Material, Accession 1996-M-133
  The materials in this accession pertain to Lerner's 1994 book, Nine Scorpions in a Bottle (originally titled Great Judges, Great Cases\). They are primarily drafts, but also include correspondence, clippings, and research materials.
  - Nine Scorpions in a Bottle (Box 1–6)
- Additional Material, Accession 1997-M-105
  - Newspaper articles/columns
    - 1943-1948 (Box 1)
    - 1940s-1970s (Box 2)
    - 1962-1968 (Box 3)
    - 1971-1978 (Box 4)
    - 1978 January-1980 August (Box 5)
    - 1980 August-1982 December (Box 6)
    - 1983-1986 June (Box 7)
    - 1986 July-1988 June (Box 8)
    - 1988 July-1990 December (Box 9)
    - 1991 January-1992 March (Box 10)
    - 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 11)
    - 1980s (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous [mostly writings], 1970s, undated (Box 13–22)
- Additional Material, Accession 2000-M-068
  - The Letters of Lincoln Steffen [annotated by Max Lerner], 1938 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession 2005-M-032
  Accession also includes 2001-M-035.
  The materials in these accessions are arranged in the following sections: correspondence, writings, teaching materials, personal, and research files and notes. An attempt has been made to maintain original order, but the accessions arrived at the repository in a random order. Some materials were contained in folders, others were not. Materials found in any given folder were kept together. When possible the handwritten titles or notes on the original folders have been used. Researchers should be advised that many folders include not only the material under which subject heading they appear, but also clippings, short writings, notes, research materials, contracts, fliers, and correspondence. Materials relating to each of Lerner's unpublished books have been placed together for ease of use.
  Correspondence is divided into subject and chronological subsections. The subject correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the name of the writer or subject of the folder. Writings include diaries, books, a screenplay, short writings, columns and lectures. The diaries and columns are arranged in chronological order, while books and short writings are in alphabetical order by title. The teaching materials are organized alphabetically by school. Personal is arranged alphabetically by subject and includes articles about Lerner, reviews of Ted and the Kennedy Legend, materials concerning his hospitalization, publicity items from his lectures, and photographs. The research notes and files are materials that Lerner may have used in the preparation of his many writings. They arrived in no discernible order. Some were in labeled folders, others were not. One box contains what appear to be random jottings on thousands of loose pages of memo pads. The research value of these materials is unknown.
  The greatest strengths of these two additions are handwritten diary entries primarily dating from the 1940s and 1988-1991, the last years of Lerner's life. The entries range in length from just a few lines to several pages. They detail Lerner's daily activities and contain his personal thoughts about his life and career. The materials from Lerner's untitled memoir, which include drafts, correspondence, and research notes, also contain reflections about his life and work, from his earliest childhood memories through his later years. The correspondence is of interest because of letters written by, or addressed, to a number of important persons from academia, politics, publishing, and other fields. The letters reflect Lerner's varied interests and multi-faceted career.
  - Correspondence
    - Subject
      - Alben, Ruth, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
      - American Civil Liberties Union, 1979-1981 (Box 1)
      - American Program Bureau, 1979-1982 (Box 1)
      - Articles, 1966-1981; 2 (Box 1)
      - Birthday (Box 1)
        - 80th, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
        - 85th, 1987 (Box 1)
      - Black, Hugo, 1966-1979 (Box 1)
      - Book gifts, 1972-1981 (Box 1)
      - Book lists and book requests, 1978-1989, undated (Box 1)
      - Bork article, 1987 (Box 1)
      - Brandeis, 1960-1983; 4 (Box 1)
      - Buckley & Hefner, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
      - Campaign-original material [1952 election], 1952, undated (Box 2)
      - China trip, 1978-1979 (Box 2)
      - College Association for Public Events and Services (CAPES), 1973-1978 (Box 2)
      - Comic books, 1953-1954 (Box 2)
      - Conference Speakers International Inc., 1980 (Box 2)
      - Europe, 1983-1988 (Box 2)
      - Europe trip, 1978 (Box 2)
      - Fulton, Richard, 1978-1984 (Box 2)
      - Harper's Magazine, 1965, undated (Box 2)
      - Harry Walker Inc., 1974-1984 (Box 2)
      - Ideas for the Ice Age, 1989-1992 (Box 2)
      - Illness, 1980-1991 (Box 2)
      - Interoffice memos, 1969-1992; 2 (Box 2)
      - Jamaica, 1974-1982 (Box 2)
      - Japan Times, 1966-1984 (Box 2)
      - Jewish Welfare Board Lecture Bureau, 1974-1985 (Box 2)
      - Johnson, Alvin, 1971 (Box 2)
      - Krishna, Gopa ["Poem to Max Lerner"], 1971-1989 (Box 3)
      - Lordly & Dane, 1978-1982 (Box 3)
      - Los Angeles Times Syndicate, 1967-1990; 6 (Box 3)
      - Memos, 1984-1991 (Box 3)
      - Pamela, 1961 (Box 3)
      - Permissions, 1980-1985 (Box 3)
      - Playboy, 1971-1991; 2 (Box 4)
      - Presidents column, 1980 (Box 4)
      - Program Corporation of America, 1978-1985 (Box 4)
      - Publishing, 1959-1990; 10 (Box 4)
      - Reader mail, 1990-1992 (Box 5)
      - Red China trip, 1971 (Box 5)
      - Responses to student letters, 1985 (Box 5)
      - Scandinavia trip, 1965 (Box 5)
      - Silver, Phyllis, 1983, undated (Box 5)
      - Southwestern University Law School, 1977-1980 (Box 5)
      - Syndicate, 1960-1989 (Box 5)
      - Ted and the Kennedy Legend, 1979-1981; 2 (Box 5)
      - Telhard Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 5)
      - United Jewish Appeal, 1974-1976 (Box 5)
      - United States International University, 1978-1986, undated; 5 (Box 5)
      - United States International University, 1987-1989, undated; 2 (Box 6)
      - Vierieck, Peter, 1952, undated (Box 6)
      - W. Colston Leigh, 1972-1976, undated (Box 6)
      - Washington Star Syndicate Contract, 1963-1967 (Box 6)
      - Washington Times, 1985-1991 (Box 6)
      - Washington University, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
      - Wrestling with the Angel, 1988-1991, undated; 6 (Box 6)
      - Wrestling with the Angel, 1990-1991, undated (Box 7)
      - Yale, 1973-1990, undated (Box 7)
    - Chronological (Box 7)
      - 1955-1970, 3 (Box 8)
      - [A-Z], 1971; 6 (Box 8)
      - 1971-1975 (Box 8)
      - 1975 (Box 8)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 8)
      - 1978-1980 (Box 8)
      - 1979-1992 (Box 8)
      - 1981 (Box 9)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 9)
      - 1982-1989 (Box 9)
      - 1984 (Box 9)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 9)
      - 1985-1990 (Box 9)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 10)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 10)
      - 1990 (Box 10)
      - 1991-1992 (Box 10)
      - Undated (Box 10)
  - Writings (Box 10)
    - Diaries (Box 10)